Guide to the Anaconda Copper Mining Company records 1876-1974
Montana Historical Society
- Boston and Montana Consolidated Copper and Silver Mining Company / Reduction Department (Great Falls)
  - Subject File
    - #1378 "Power requirements for Zinc Plant", 1918-1920 (Box-folder 297 / 2)
    - #1380 "Safety First Department: annual accident reports", 1965-1968 (Box-folder 297 / 3)
    - #1381 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate", 1918-1966 (Box-folder 297 / 4-7)
    - #1381-2 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Butte & Superior Copper Co.", 1918-1940 (Box-folder 297 / 8)
    - #1381-3 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Anselmo Mining Corp.", 1923-1958 (Box-folder 297 / 9)
    - #1381-4 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Timber Butte Milling Co.", 1918-1939 (Box-folder 297 / 10)
    - #1381-5 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Federal Mining and Smelting Co.", 1923-1946 (Box-folder 298 / 1-3)
    - #1381-6 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Granite-BiMetallic Consolidated Mining Co.", 1919-1936 (Box-folder 298 / 4)
    - #1381-7 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Highland-Surprise", 1923-1950 (Box-folder 298 / 5)
    - #1381-8 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Callahan Zinc-Lead Co.", 1918-1948 (Box-folder 298 / 6)
    - #1381-9 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Main Range ore", 1919-1920 (Box-folder 298 / 7)
    - #1381-10 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Midvale Mineral Co.", 1919-1935 (Box-folder 298 / 8)
    - #1381-11 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Moulton ore", 1919-1920 (Box-folder 298 / 9)
    - #1381-12 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Philipsburg ore", 1922-1933 (Box-folder 298 / 10)
    - #1381-13 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Snowstorm ore", 1918-1929 (Box-folder 298 / 11)
    - #1381-14 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Success Mining Co.", 1921-1928 (Box-folder 298 / 12)
    - #1381-15 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Sidney Leasing Co.", 1923-1948 (Box-folder 298 / 13)
    - #1381-17 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Emma ore", 1915-1939 (Box-folder 298 / 14-15)
    - #1381-17 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Emma ore", 1940-1959 (Box-folder 299 / 1)
    - #1381-18 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Hibernia ore", 1921 (Box-folder 299 / 2)
    - #1381-19 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Elkhorn ore", 1918-1920 (Box-folder 299 / 3)
    - #1381-20 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Constitution Mining & Milling Co.", 1923-1941 (Box-folder 299 / 4-5)
    - #1381-21 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Nabob ore", 1923-1925 (Box-folder 299 / 6)
    - #1381-22 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Trail concentrates", 1923-1969 (Box-folder 299 / 7-8)
    - #1381-23 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Silver King Coalition Mines Co.", 1923-1945 (Box-folder 299 / 9)
    - #1381-24 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Judge Mining and Smelting Co. (Park Utah Consol. Mines Co.)", 1924-1950 (Box-folder 299 / 10)
    - #1381-25 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: U.S. Smelting, Refining, and Mining Co.", 1923-1931 (Box-folder 299 / 11)
    - #1381-25 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: U.S. Smelting, Refining, and Mining Co.", 1923-1931 (Box-folder 300 / 1)
    - #1381-26 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Combined Metals Reduction Co.", 1924-1967 (Box-folder 300 / 2-3)
    - #1381-27 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: McBarron ore", 1924-1927 (Box-folder 300 / 4)
    - #1381-28 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Hecla Mining Co. (Star Mine)", 1924-1942 (Box-folder 300 / 5)
    - #1381-28 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Hecla Mining Co. (Red Cloud Mines, Inc.), 1943-1966 (Box-folder 300 / 6)
    - #1381-29 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Paul V. Dovek ore", 1924-1926 (Box-folder 300 / 7)
    - #1381-30 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: John Makynen and Co.", 1924-1926 (Box-folder 300 / 8)
    - #1381-32 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: diversion of excess concentrates", 1924-1937 (Box-folder 300 / 9)
    - #1381-33 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Blue Ridge Mining Co.", 1924-1926 (Box-folder 300 / 10)
    - #1381-34 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Rex Mine", 1924-1926 (Box-folder 301 / 1)
    - #1381-35 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Utah-Apex Mining Co.", 1924-1931 (Box-folder 301 / 2)
    - #1381-36 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Chief Consolidated Mining Co.", 1924-1960 (Box-folder 301 / 3)
    - #1381-38 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: East Butte Copper Mining Co.", 1926 (Box-folder 301 / 4)
    - #1381-39 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Rising Star ore", 1926 (Box-folder 301 / 5)
    - #1381-40 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Pend Oreille Lead and Zinc Co.", 1927-1950 (Box-folder 301 / 6)
    - #1381-41 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Hercules Mining Co." (re Tamarack, Custer, and Day mines, etc.), 1923-1963 (Box-folder 301 / 7-8)
    - #1381-42 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Rico ore", 1927-1929 (Box-folder 301 / 9)
    - #1381-43 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Canyon Creek Milling Co.", 1928 (Box-folder 301 / 10)
    - #1381-44 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Whitehurst and Madzgalla", 1926-1928 (Box-folder 301 / 11)
    - #1381-45 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Golconda Lead Mines Co.", 1928-1947 (Box-folder 301 / 12)
    - #1381-46 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: St. Joseph Lead Co." (re Hughesville), 1928-1946 (Box-folder 301 / 13)
    - #1381-47 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Johnson-Sallee lease", 1940-1941 (Box-folder 301 / 14)
    - #1381-49 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Sunset Mine", 1940-1962 (Box-folder 301 / 15)
    - #1381-51 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Irma Mines, Inc. (Cooke City), 1940-1952 (Box-folder 301 / 16)
    - #1381-52 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Metals Reserve Co. / Domestic Manganese and Development Co.", 1944-1961 (Box-folder 301 / 17)
    - #1381-53 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Clayton Silver Mines", 1941-1972 (Box-folder 301 / 18)
    - #1381-54 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Lexington Mining Co." (Neihart), 1942-1956 (Box-folder 302 / 1)
    - #1381-55 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Victoria Mines, Inc." (Sheridan), 1939-1962 (Box-folder 302 / 2)
    - #1381-56 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Bennett Mining Co." (Neihart), 1943-1955 (Box-folder 302 / 3)
    - #1381-57 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Mountain Copper Co." (Mattie ore), 1944-1965 (Box-folder 302 / 4)
    - #1381-58 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Eagle Shawmut Mine", 1945-1947 (Box-folder 302 / 5)
    - #1381-59 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: American Zinc, Lead, and Smelting Co.", 1939-1970 (Box-folder 302 / 6)
    - #1381-60 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Star Mine and Mill" (Neihart), 1947-1962 (Box-folder 302 / 7)
    - #1381-61 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Big Four Mining Co.", 1946-1951 (Box-folder 302 / 8)
    - #1381-62 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Deer Lodge Mining Co.", 1947-1952 (Box-folder 302 / 9)
    - #1381-63 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Sullivan Mining Co.", 1948-1950 (Box-folder 302 / 10)
    - #1381-64 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Darwin Mines", 1948-1972 (Box-folder 302 / 11)
    - #1381-65 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Saranac Mining Co." (Maxville), 1948-1958 (Box-folder 302 / 12)
    - #1381-66 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Victor Development Co.", 1948-1949 (Box-folder 302 / 13)
    - #1381-68 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Coronado Copper & Zinc Co.", 1948-1952 (Box-folder 302 / 14)
    - #1381-71 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Denver Development Co.", 1948-1949 (Box-folder 302 / 15)
    - #1381-74 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Kings Hill Mining Co." (Neihart), 1948-1949 (Box-folder 302 / 16)
    - #1381-75 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Sherman mine" (Neihart), 1949-1951 (Box-folder 302 / 17)
    - #1381-76 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Kuhlman Die Casting Co.", 1950-1951 (Box-folder 302 / 18)
    - #1381-77 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Glenn Zorn ore" (Butte), 1950-1951 (Box-folder 302 / 19)
    - #1381-78 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Wayne Miller ore" (Radersburg), 1951-1952 (Box-folder 302 / 20)
    - #1381-79 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: U.S. Mining Co." (Neihart), 1951-1952 (Box-folder 302 / 21)
    - #1381-80 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Metal Producers, Inc.", 1951-1952 (Box-folder 302 / 22)
    - #1381-81 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Sun Valley Lead-Silver Mines, Inc.", 1951-1952 (Box-folder 302 / 23)
    - #1381-82 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: American Metal Climax", 1952-1972 (Box-folder 302 / 24)
    - #1381-83 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Metals Milling Co." (Basin), 1952 (Box-folder 302 / 25)
    - #1381-84 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Taylor-Knapp Co." (Philipsburg), 1953-1960 (Box-folder 302 / 26)
    - #1381-85 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Joe T. Farrell concentrates" (Neihart), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 303 / 1)
    - #1381-85 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Mitchell Mining Co." (Butte), 1952-1962 (Box-folder 303 / 2)
    - #1381-85 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Philipp Brothers", 1955-1970 (Box-folder 303 / 3-4)
    - #1381-85 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Samincorp", 1950-1969 (Box-folder 303 / 5-6)
    - #1381-88 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Samincorp", 1950-1969 (Box-folder 303 / 5-6)
    - #1381-89 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: C. Tennant, Sons & Co.), 1963-1966 (Box-folder 303 / 7)
    - #1381-91 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: U.S. Steel Corp.), 1964 (Box-folder 303 / 8)
    - #1381-92 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Canadian Exploration Co.", 1965-1969 (Box-folder 303 / 9)
    - #1381-93 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: Federal Resources Corp.", 1965-1972 (Box-folder 303 / 10)
    - #1381-94 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: West Hill Exploration", 1967 (Box-folder 303 / 11)
    - #1381-98 "Contracts for purchase of zinc ore and concentrate: New Jersey Zinc Co.", 1970 (Box-folder 303 / 12)
    - #1382 "Zinc Plant shipments: Zinc Plant residue to American Smelting and Refining Co., East Helena", 1934-1970 (Box-folder 303 / 13-14)
    - #1383-1 "Zinc Plant residue", 1919-1970 (Box-folder 304 / 1)
    - #1383-2 "Zinc Plant residue: storage or smelting at Great Falls v. shipment to East Helena and Tooele", 1918-1955 (Box-folder 304 / 2)
    - #1383-3 "Zinc Plant residue: cost of repulping & leaching zinc residue", 1919 (Box-folder 304 / 3)
    - #1383-4 "Zinc Plant residue: flotation or residue & classifier sand" (re tailings), 1918-1941 (Box-folder 304 / 4)
    - #1383-5 "Zinc Plant residue: salt leaching for recovery of lead & silver", 1916-1935 (Box-folder 304 / 5)
    - #1383-7 "Zinc Plant residue: sulphuric acid leaching & fuming", 1918-1937 (Box-folder 304 / 6)
    - #1383-8 "Zinc Plant residue: repulping & filtering zinc residue to improve recovery", 1920-1953 (Box-folder 304 / 7)
    - #1383-9 "Zinc Plant residue: experimental electric smelting in Westly type furnace", 1922-1924 (Box-folder 304 / 8)
    - #1383-10 "Zinc Plant residue: strong acid leaching of residue & installation of process equipment", 1924-1968 (Box-folder 304 / 9)
    - #1383-10 "Zinc Plant residue: strong acid leaching of residue & installation of process equipment" [Archives Map Case], 1924-1968 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1383-11 "Zinc Plant residue: leaching of roasting purification cake and installation of process equipment", 1924-1959 (Box-folder 305 / 1)
    - #1383-12 "Zinc Plant residue: electric smelting in 50-ton furnace", 1924-1928 (Box-folder 305 / 2)
    - #1383-12 "Zinc Plant residue: electirc smelting in 50-ton furnace" [Archives Map Case], 1924-1928 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1383-13 "Zinc Plant residue: Mayer-Lamotte sulphuric acid treatment of zinc slag and zinc residue", 1926-1927 (Box-folder 305 / 3)
    - #1383-14 "Zinc Plant residue: treatment at Anaconda v. shipment to East Helena", 1927-1930 (Box-folder 305 / 4)
    - #1384 "Tainton-Pring electrolytic zinc process, including magnetic concentration", 1919-1950 (Box-folder 305 / 5)
    - #1385 "Using electric furnaces for manufacture of ferro-chrome", 1918-1941 (Box-folder 305 / 6)
    - #1386 "Using electric furnaces for manufacture of ferro-silicon", 1918-1942 (Box-folder 305 / 7)
    - #1387 "Supplies for carbide manufacture", 1918-1930 (Box-folder 305 / 8)
    - #1388 "Melting of zinc cathodes", 1919-1960 (Box-folder 305 / 9-10)
    - #1388 "Melting of zinc cathodes" [Archives Map Case], 1919-1960 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1388 "Melting of zinc cathodes", 1961-1970 (Box-folder 306 / 1-2)
    - #1388 "Melting of zinc cathodes" (misc. files), 1921-1952 (Box-folder 306 / 3)
    - #1388 "Melting of zinc cathodes" (miscellanous files) [Archives Map Case], 1921-1952 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1388-8 "Melting of zinc cathodes: Ajax furnace for production of alloy zinc", 1952-1960 (Box-folder 306 / 4)
    - #1388-8 "Melting of zinc cathodes: Ajax furnace for production of alloy zinc" [Archives Map Case], 1952-1960 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1389 "Zinc Plant leaching plant", 1919-1960 (Box-folder 306 / 5-8)
    - #1389 "Zinc Plant leachinig plant" [Archives Map Case], 1919-1960 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1389 "Zinc Plant leaching plant", 1961-1970 (Box-folder 307 / 1-3)
    - #1389 "Zinc Plant leachinig plant" [Archives Map Case], 1961-1970 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1389 "Zinc Plant leaching plant: union", 1956-1970 (Box-folder 307 / 4)
    - #1389-3 "Zinc Plant leaching plant: slimes in neutral Dorr overflow", 1952-1954 (Box-folder 307 / 5)
    - #1389-4 "Zinc Plant leaching plant: direct leaching of green purification residue", 1958-1968 (Box-folder 307 / 6)
    - #1389-4 "Zinc Plant leachinig plant: direct leaching of green purification residue" [Archives Map Case], 1958-1968 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1391 "Welfare Department", 1918-1937 (Box-folder 307 / 7-8)
    - #1391-2 "Welfare Department: welfare work of outside companies", 1919-1959 (Box-folder 308 / 1)
    - #1391-3 "Welfare Department: medical examination and classification of employees", 1919-1965 (Box-folder 308 / 2)
    - #1391-5 "Welfare Department: foremanship conferences under auspices of Federal Board for Vocational Education", 1922-1935 (Box-folder 308 / 3)
    - #1391-6 "Welfare Department: Citizens' Relief Committee", 1932-1933 (Box-folder 308 / 4)
    - #1391-7 "Welfare Department: group insurance", 1936-1969 (Box-folder 308 / 5-6)
    - #1391-8 "Welfare Department: Community Chest", 1932-1968 (Box-folder 308 / 7-8)
    - #1391-9 "Welfare Department: hospital, surgical and medical insurance", 1960-1965 (Box-folder 309 / 1)
    - #1391-10 "Welfare Department: United Way", 1969-1971 (Box-folder 309 / 2)
    - #1392 "Wire", 1918-1935 (Box-folder 309 / 3)
    - #1393 "Subscriptions: War Chest Fund, Deer Lodge County", 1918 (Box-folder 309 / 4)
    - #1393-2 "Subscriptions: Salvation Army", 1919-1967 (Box-folder 309 / 5)
    - #1393-3 "Subscriptions: Montana Livestock Pavilion Company", 1919-1938 (Box-folder 309 / 6)
    - #1394 "Supplies for zinc oxide manufacture", 1919-1920 (Box-folder 309 / 7)
    - #1397 "Hanley methods for production of zinc and cadmium", 1917-1933 (Box-folder 309 / 8)
    - #1399-2 "Laist-Elton electrolytic zinc process: description for Mechanical Engineering Handbook", 1923-1945 (Box-folder 309 / 9)
    - #1399-3 "Laist-Elton electrolytic zinc process: description for American Electrochemical Society", 1923-1924 (Box-folder 309 / 10)
    - #1400 "Elton-Caples process for production of cadmium", 1919-1930 (Box-folder 309 / 11)
    - #1401 "Zinc Plant: price of zinc sales", 1918-1968 (Box-folder 309 / 12)
    - #1401 "Zinc Plant: price of zinc sales" [Archives Map Case], 1918-1968 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1403 "Zinc Plant: zinc production reported to American Zinc Institute", 1920-1952 (Box-folder 309 / 13)
    - #1406-1 "Rolling Mills Department: scrap and scale", 1919-1944 (Box-folder 309 / 14)
    - #1406-2 "Rolling Mills Department: scrap and scale shipments to furnace refinery", 1920-1959 (Box-folder 309 / 15)
    - #1414 "Calcine shipments from Anaconda", 1920-1949 (Box-folder 310 / 1)
    - #1416 "Fire insurance policies for Rolling Mills Department", 1918-1961 (Box-folder 310 / 2)
    - #1426 "Production, stock in hand & regulation of Rolling Mills to meet disposition orders", 1957-1967 (Box-folder 310 / 3)
    - #1427 "Defective wirebar", 1960-1965 (Box-folder 310 / 4)
    - #1428-2 "Brick Plant: sales of brick by county", 1913-1919 (Box-folder 310 / 5)
    - #1428-3 "Brick Plant: daily record of operation, production, and stock in hand", 1917-1918 (Box-folder 310 / 6)
    - #1430-1 "Zinc Plant solutions", 1921-1927 (Box-folder 310 / 7)
    - #1430-2 "Zinc Plant solutions: evaporation of cell solution", 1919-1954 (Box-folder 310 / 8)
    - #1431 "American smelting & Refining Co.: shipment of zinc residue to East Helena & lead bullion to East Chicago", 1918-1957 (Box-folder 310 / 9-11)
    - #1431 "American smelting & Refining Co.: shipment of zinc residue to East Helena & lead bullion to East Chicago", 1958-1970 (Box-folder 311 / 1)
    - #1435 "Safety First Committee meetings: Zinc Plant", 1932-1961 (Box-folder 311 / 2)
    - #1436 "Cost of producing zinc from custom zinc concentrates" (misc. files), 1918-1938 (Box-folder 311 / 3-4)
    - #1437-1 "Metal Roofing Department: copper & zinc shingles", 1913-1959 (Box-folder 311 / 5)
    - #1437-2 "Metal Roofing Department: copper & bronze nails", 1921-1964 (Box-folder 311 / 6)
    - #1437-4 "Metal Roofing Department: electrolytic deposition of shingle copper", 1921-1940 (Box-folder 311 / 7)
    - #1438 "Manufacture of phosphoric acid", 1921-1923 (Box-folder 311 / 8)
    - #1443 "Laist-Elton electrolytic zinc process: alleged infringement on Betts patent", 1922 (Box-folder 311 / 9)
    - #1444 "Copper cathodes shipped to American Brass Company", 1922-1960 (Box-folder 311 / 10)
    - #1445 "Electrolytic process v. retort process for zinc extraction", 1921-1952 (Box-folder 311 / 11)
    - #1446 "Treatment of Magnus zinc oxide by Laist-Elton electrolytic zinc process", 1921-1922 (Box-folder 312 / 1)
    - #1448 "Shipments of lead bullion from American Smelting and Refining Co. to International Lead Refining Co.", 1939-1945 (Box-folder 312 / 2)
    - #1450 "Construction & installation at Zinc Plant" (misc. files), 1919-1923 (Box-folder 312 / 3)
    - #1450-5 "Construction & installation at Zinc Plant: proposed extensions", 1919-1923 (Box-folder 312 / 3)
    - #1450-6 "Construction & installation at Zinc Plant: Tooele, Anaconda, Great Falls", 1926-1963 (Box-folder 312 / 4)
    - #1451 "Complaints regarding quality of copper", 1923-1932 (Box-folder 312 / 5-9)
    - #1451 "Complaints regarding quality of copper", 1933-1958 (Box-folder 313 / 1-2)
    - #1452 "Rolling Mills Department: bonus system...to increase production", 1922-1969 (Box-folder 313 / 3)
    - #1452 "Rolling Mills Department: bonus system...to increase production: aluminum wire", 1950-1964 (Box-folder 313 / 4-5)
    - #1452-7 "Rolling Mills Department: bonus system...to increase production: recapitulation of payroll", 1946-1970 (Box-folder 313 / 6)
    - #1453 "Wire & cable manufactured by Rolling Mills Dept." (re Rural Electrification Administration projects), 1932-1953 (Box-folder 313 / 7)
    - #1453-3 "Wire & cable manufactured by Rolling Mills Dept.: transmission cable for Ft. Peck Dam", 1934 (Box-folder 314 / 1)
    - #1453-4 "Wire & cable manufactured by Rolling Mills Dept.: aluminum", 1950-1959 (Box-folder 314 / 2)
    - #1454 "Proposed zinc plant in Coeur d'Alene or Spokane district", 1922-1948 (Box-folder 314 / 3)
    - #1458 "Zinc dross shipments to National Zinc Co.", 1929-1930 (Box-folder 314 / 4)
    - #1460 "Safety First Dept.: first aid contests", 1923-1968 (Box-folder 314 / 5-9)
    - #1461 "Moroney Natatorium at Great Falls" (re swimming pool), 1917-1923 (Box-folder 314 / 10)
    - #1461 "Moroney Natatorium at Great Falls" (re swimming pool) [Archives Map Case], 1919-1960 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1463 "Zinc Oxide Plant: tonnage requirements of zinc & zinc dross", 1921-1924 (Box-folder 315 / 1)
    - #1468 "Cost of producing zinc from Anselmo ore", 1923-1924 (Box-folder 315 / 2)
    - #1473 "Purchase & sale of silver under Pittman Act", 1922-1940 (Box-folder 315 / 3)
    - #1481 "Retail food prices", 1937-1943 (Box-folder 315 / 4)
    - #1482 "Fuel oil supply for Great Falls plant", 1923-1965 (Box-folder 315 / 5)
    - #1482-2 "Fuel oil supply for Great Falls plant: Sunburst Refining Co.", 1923-1932 (Box-folder 315 / 6)
    - #1482-2 "Fuel oil supply for Great Falls plant: Sunburst Refining Co." [Archives Map Case], 1923-1932 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1482-3 "Fuel oil supply for Great Falls plant: Julian Petroleum Co.", 1926-1930 (Box-folder 315 / 7)
    - #1486 "Complaints regarding quality of cadmium", 1923-1938 (Box-folder 315 / 8)
    - #1488 "Treatment costs of lead bullion at International Lead Refining Co.", 1924-1946 (Box-folder 315 / 9)
    - #1489 "Cost of refining & casting Tooele copper bullion into anodes at Anaconda....", 1923-1947 (Box-folder 315 / 10)
    - #1490 "Concentrate shipments: lead concentrate to Tooele & East Helena", 1923-1958 (Box-folder 315 / 11)
    - #1492 "Handball courts for employees", 1925-1926 (Box-folder 315 / 12)
    - #1493 Penarroya Zinc Plant, 1918-1925 (Box-folder 315 / 13)
    - #1493 Penarroya Zinc Plant, 1926 (Box-folder 316 / 1)
    - #1495 "A.G. French zinc process patent", 1909-1952 (Box-folder 316 / 2)
    - #1496 "Compaignie royale Asturienne des Mines (Det Norske Zinkkomani)" (re Norwegian plant), 1926-1928 (Box-folder 316 / 3-6)
    - #1496 "Compaignie royale Asturienne des Mines (Det Norske Zinkkomani)" (re Norwegian plant) [Archives Map Case], 1926-1928 (Oversize-folder 7)
    - #1496 "Compaignie royale Asturienne des Mines (Det Norske Zinkkomani)" (re Norwegian plant), 1928-1964 (Box-folder 317 / 1-2)
    - #1497 "Proposed 70-ton electrolytic zinc plant at Spencer, Idaho", 1926 (Box-folder 317 / 3)
    - #1498 "Purchase of von Giesche property in Poland (Geische Spolka Akcyjma)", 1925-1947 (Box-folder 317 / 4)
    - #1499 "Great Falls Brick & Tile Co. takeover by W.H. Gunniss", 1927-1944 (Box-folder 317 / 5)
    - #1500 "Electrolytic zinc process as applied to Joplin-Miami zinc concentrate" (includes proposed plant), 1925-1944 (Box-folder 317 / 6)
    - #1504 "Experimental work done & results obtained at Great Falls & Raritan", 1928-1942 (Box-folder 317 / 7-8)